top of page

* More...

Use tab to navigate through the menu items.

Privacy Policy
==============

​

All personal contact information shared with Together for Choice from online forms is stored in a secure database. Only authorized representatives of Together for Choice will have access to your personal information. We will never share your personal information with third parties unless required by law.

Together for Choice does not collect any financial information from our web users. All financial information is collected by PayPal or other payment processors unless it is mailed to Together for Choice, in which case financial information is securely stored and inaccessible except by employees of Together for Choice’s participating organizations.

Website user data collected by Together for Choice is not traceable to individual users.

By joining Together for Choice’s email list (which you automatically join upon becoming a member), you will receive periodic emails from us related to our mission and work. You may unsubscribe from these emails at any time.

If you would like Together for Choice to change or delete any personal information you have already shared with us, or for any other privacy-related questions, please contact us.

### We respect your right to privacy

We must come together and advocate for  
high-quality life options for people with I/DD.    
  
Join Our Movement   
 
======================================================================================================================

### Together for Choice

6050 S. Buffalo Drive  
Las Vegas, NV 89113-2154

​

Tax ID: 82-2128631

#### [About US](https://www.togetherforchoice.org/aboutus)

#### [Resources](https://www.togetherforchoice.org/)

#### [Membership](https://www.togetherforchoice.org/ga-membership)

#### [Connect](https://www.togetherforchoice.org/contact-us)

#### [Policy Statement](https://www.togetherforchoice.org/policystatement)

#### [FAQs](https://www.togetherforchoice.org/faqs)

#### [Privacy Policy](https://www.togetherforchoice.org/terms-of-use)

bottom of page
